Clement F. Haynsworth Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- United States Court of Appeals File, 1955-1989 (Box 6-201)
  - Case File, 1956-1989 (Box 7-159)
    - 1980 October term
      - Lawson v. Andrews, No. 80-1399
      - Potter Instrument Co. v. Storage Technology Co., No. 80-1428
      - Engle v. McDonnell Douglas Corp., No. 80-1438
      - Sere v. Welsh, No. 80-1470
      - Allard v. Immigration and Naturalization Serv., No. 80-1476
      - Federal Deposit Ins. Corp. v. Coachwood Invs., No. 80-1498
      - Robinson v. Marine Towing & Transp. Co., No. 80-1506
      - Fike v. United Methodist Children's Home, No. 80-1513
      - Azzara v. Norfolk and W. Ry., No. 80-1515
      - Tyler v. United States, No. 80-1516
      - Pledger v. Raymond-Dravo-Langenfelder, No. 80-1528
      - Van Sant v. United States, No. 80-1531
      - Allard v. Petersam, No. 80-1570; (2 folders) (Box 76)
      - Major v. Orthopedic Equip. Co., No. 80-1604
      - Independent Ins. Agents of Am. v. Board of Governors, Fed. Reserve Sys., No. 80-1611
      - Davis v. Commissioner, No. 80-1613
      - Libbie Convalescent Center v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 80-1633
      - Kuykendall v. Southern Ry., No. 80-1642
      - Inta-Roto, Inc. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 80-1692
      - Marshall v. Seaward Int'l, No. 80-1708
      - In re Daye, No. 80-1714
      - Figg v. Hewlett, No. 80-1720
      - Colby v. Halperin, No. 80-1721
      - Bates v. Clements, No. 80-1728
      - United States v. Shriver, No. 80-1733
      - Hopper v. Aetna Auto., Life and Casualty, No. 80-1742
      - Malek Abdullah Malek-Marzban v. Immigration and Naturalization Serv., No. 80-1779
      - Aeronca, Inc. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 80-1802
      - Herbert v. Califano, No. 80-1811
      - Barber v. Harris, No. 80-1833
      - Alexander v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 80-1873 (Box 77)
      - United States v. Hawkins, No. 80-5021
      - United States v. Shamy, No. 80-5056
      - United States v. Pace, No. 80-5070
      - United States v. Graziano, No. 80-5089
      - United States v. Hines, No. 80-5097
      - United States v. Metz, No. 80-5118
      - United States v. Riggs, No. 80-5171
      - United States v. Snead, No. 80-5175
      - United States v. Hicks, No. 80-5225; (3 folders)
      - Carey v. Lally, No. 80-6072
      - United States v. Ledson, No. 80-6160
      - Cumber v. Winters, No. 80-6191
      - United States v. Mason, No. 80-6219
      - Ganey v. Futch, No. 80-6265
      - Marsh v. Maryland, No. 80-6286 (Box 78)
      - Ingram v. Pruitt, No. 80-6287
      - Robinson v. Cabell, No. 80-6293
      - Taylor v. Reed, No. 80-6348
      - Truslow v. Reynolds, No. 80-6364
      - Edwards v. Gibson, No. 80-6370
      - Sewell v. Virginia Parole Bd., No. 80-6483
      - Banks v. Sutton, No. 80-6499
      - Allen v. Peters, No. 80-6510
      - Smith v. DeHart, No. 80-6520
      - United States v. Hawkins, No. 80-6525
      - McKinney v. Smith, No. 80-6528
      - Shaw v. Walker, No. 80-6541
      - Goode v. Peebles, No. 80-6551
      - McNeil v. Tillery, No. 80-6552
      - Holloway v. United States, No. 80-6553
      - Scott v. Collins, No. 80-6574
      - Medlock v. Hinton, No. 80-6582
      - United States v. Dumeur, No. 80-6616
      - Evans v. Garrison, No. 80-6622
      - Ward v. Southall, No. 80-6629
      - Bratten v. Smith, No. 80-6631
      - Stevens v. Kirkpatrick, No. 80-6645
      - Pate v. Edmonds, No. 80-6657
      - Bryant v. Maryland, No. 80-6658
      - Nelson v. Farmer, No. 80-6668
      - Dallas v. Loyd, No. 80-6669
      - Talley v. Gathright, No. 80-6677
      - United States v. Martino, No. 80-6680
      - Carter v. Garrison, No. 80-6696
      - Hudson v. Blankenship, No. 80-6703
      - United States v. Williams, No. 80-6706
      - United States v. Curry, No. 80-6707 (Box 79)
      - Gardner v. Hewitt, No. 80-6710
      - Perkins v. Loving, No. 80-6725
      - Drysdale v. Broughton, No. 80-6771
      - Vance v. Hedrick, No. 80-6800
      - West v. McRae, No. 80-6810
      - Wallace v. Mitchell, No. 80-8089
      - Watkins v. Martin, No. 80-8117
      - Hudspeth v. Superintendent, James River Correctional Center, No. 80-8134
      - Gary v. Stevenson, No. 80-8173
      - Coleman v. Hutto, No. 80-8206
      - Berry v. Wyant, No. 80-8232
      - Alexander v. Bordenkircher, No. 80-8233
      - Abernathy v. Garrison, No. 80-8261
      - Murray v. Edwards, No. 80-8267
      - Dillard v. Martin, No. 80-8273
      - Atkins v. West Virginia, No. 80-8298
      - Walker v. Garraghty, No. 80-8316
      - Davis v. Maryland, No. 80-8319
      - Gay v. Reed, No. 80-8322
      - Smith v. Garrison, No. 80-8349
      - Citicorp Person-to-Person Fin. Corp. v. Brazell, No. 81-1003
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Cumberland Nursing & Convalescent Center, No. 81-1037
      - Jarrell v. Harris, No. 81-1083
      - Federal Trade Comm'n v. Virginia Homes Corp., No. 81-1187
      - Benford v. American Broadcasting Cos., No. 81-1200
      - Dallas v. Estees, No. 81-1258
      - Johns v. Scherr, No. 81-1352
      - In re Smith, No. 81-1576 (Box 80)
      - Ashby v. Federal Bureau of Investigation, No. 81-1666
      - United States v. Marable, No. 81-5001
      - United States v. King, No. 81-5037
      - United States v. Elliott, No. 81-5051
      - In re Crocker, No. 81-5097
      - Crenshaw v. Leeke, No. 81-6001
      - Taylor v. Collins, No. 81-6033
      - Slade v. Garrison, No. 81-6039
      - Grubbs v. Burke, No. 81-6079
      - Pryor v. United States Parole Office, No. 81-6099
      - Green v. Stovall, No. 81-6116
      - Richardson v. Wheeler, No. 81-6122
      - Kelly v. Davis, No. 81-6131
      - United States v. Williams, No. 81-6140
      - Buchanan v. Leeke, No. 81-6145
      - Crump v. Turner, No. 81-6163
      - Burleson v. Keith, No. 81-6164
      - United States v. Brooks, No. 81-6172
      - McBride v. Smith, No. 81-6231
      - Boyd v. Mitchell, No. 81-6254
      - Williams v. Bloom, No. 81-6259
      - Brown v. Kelly, No. 81-6273
      - Greene v. Gurley, No. 81-6295
      - Tanner v. Maryland State Police, No. 81-6298
      - Dallas v. Jonas, No. 81-6325
      - Adamson v. Gathright, No. 81-6339
      - Dallas v. Barefoot, No. 81-6351
      - Thomas v. Allsbrook, No. 81-6364
      - Honeycutt v. Johnson, No. 81-6381
      - Fleming v. Spruill, No. 81-6427
      - Ellard v. McKenzie, No. 81-6519
      - Drake v. Virginia Probation & Parole Bd., No. 81-6560
      - Hughes v. Clawson, No. 81-6735
      - Lamp v. Mohn, No. 81-8027
      - Walker v. Superintendent, Bland Correctional Center, No. 81-8122
      - Spight v. Garrison, No. 81-8149
      - Holliday v. Bordenkircher, No. 81-8195 (Box 81)
      - Grandison v. Maryland, No. 81-8217
    - 1981 October term
      - Fehlhaber v. North Carolina, No. 78-1112
      - J. P. Stevens & Co. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 79-1502
      - Allen v. McCutcheon, No. 79-1802
      - United States v. Paugh, No. 79-5203
      - United States v. MacDonald, No. 79-5253; (5 folders)
      - United States v. Hinnant, No. 79-5255
      - United States v. Barber, No. 79-5278
      - United States v. Steed, No. 79-5294; (2 folders) (Box 82)
      - United States v. Hurn, No. 79-5318
      - United States v. Kibler, No. 79-5337
      - United States v. Means, No. 79-5345
      - Prosise v. Haring, No. 79-6310
      - Lebedun v. Young, No. 79-6344
      - Walker v. Kendall, No. 79-6515
      - Short v. Emerson, No. 79-6701
      - Blankenship v. Schweiker, No. 80-1019
      - Federal Deposit Ins. Corp. v. Fagan, No. 80-1050
      - Reid v. Pierce Ditching Co., No. 80-1178
      - Moosavi v. Fairfax County Bd. of Educ., No. 80-1283
      - Master Printers of Am. v. Marshall, No. 80-1578
      - United Glass and Ceramic Workers of N. Am. v. AFG Indus., No. 80-1679
      - Tart v. City of Chesapeake, No. 80-1727
      - Bowers v. Commissioner, No. 80-1759
      - Roco Worldwide v. Constellation Navigation, No. 80-1781 (Box 83)
      - Logan v. Shealy, No. 80-1815
      - United States v. O'Conner, No. 80-1817
      - Methodist Home v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 80-1839
      - Consolidation Coal Co. v. Marshall, No. 80-1862
      - Terry v. Norfolk and W. Ry., No. 80-1874
      - Copper v. Fitzgerald, No. 80-1878
      - United States v. Goodwin, No. 80-5116
      - United States v. Woodfin, No. 80-5223
      - United States v. Pettee, No. 80-5229
      - Strong v. Hutto, No. 80-6204
      - Clayton v. Hicks, No. 80-6290
      - Cross v. Harvey, No. 80-6397
      - Ruffin v. Hutto, No. 80-6406
      - Talbott v. Cochran, No. 80-6471
      - Person v. Sanders, No. 80-6505
      - Ruplenas v. Swinson, No. 80-6562
      - Shaw v. Hodge, No. 80-6590
      - Street v. Cherba, No. 80-6611
      - Shaw v. Terry, No. 80-6728
      - Anderson v. Turner, No. 80-8155
      - Safrit v. Garrison, No. 80-8203
      - Holsey v. Keller, No. 80-8224
      - Hedrick v. Allsbrook, No. 80-8258
      - Eliason v. Hinton, No. 80-8263
      - Walton v. Mohn, No. 80-8276
      - Sullivan v. Leeke, No. 80-8337
      - American Honda Motor Corp. v. Jonas, No. 81-1024 (Box 84)
      - North Carolina Elec. Membership Corp. v. Carolina Power & Light Co., No. 81-1057
      - Brady v. Thurston Motor Lines, No. 81-1060
      - Williams v. United States, No. 81-1064
      - Ranger Fuel Corp. v. Youghiogheny and Ohio Coal Co., No. 81-1084
      - St. Charles Mfg. Co. v. St. Charles of Carolina, No. 81-1101
      - Joers v. United States, No. 81-1108
      - National R.R. Passenger Corp. v. One 32.5+ Parcel of land, Anne Arundel County, No. 81-1126
      - Howard v. Sylvester, No. 81-1166
      - Newport News Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Co. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 81-1167
      - Cary v. Defense Logistics Agency, No. 81-1176
      - Cooke v. School Bd., City of Newport News, No. 81-1196
      - Pants Rack v. United States, No. 81-1231
      - Adams Laboratories v. Askew, No. 81-1232
      - Adams Laboratories v. Garrett, No. 81-1233
      - Dalton v. Employment Sec. Comm'n, No. 81-1242
      - Newport News Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Co. v. Equal Employment Opportunity Comm'n, No. 81-1283; (1 folder) (Box 85)
      - Wallace v. Nationwide Mut. Fire Ins. Co., No. 81-1289
      - Pritchett v. Schweiker, No. 81-1294
      - Price v. Mendenhall, No. 81-1300
      - Trustees, Nat'l Benefit Fund for Hosp. and Health Care Employees v. Constant Care Community Health Center, No. 81-1318
      - Newport News Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Co. v. Director, Office of Workers' Compensation Programs, No. 81-1323
      - PPG Indus. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 81-1329
      - Solazzi v. Virginia Polytechnic Inst. and State Univ., No. 81-1351
      - Ashby v. Various Persons, No. 81-1442
      - Home Indem. Co. v. Stanfield, No. 81-1443
      - Johnson v. A. H. Robins Co., No. 81-1445
      - Smithwick v. Alexander, No. 81-1464
      - Stalans v. National Sec. Agency, No. 81-1493
      - International Tel. & Tel. Corp. v. Union Carbide Corp., No. 81-1506
      - Backus v. Spears, No. 81-1517
      - Humphrey v. Langford, No. 81-1540
      - Diversified Mortgage Invs. v. First Charter Land Corp., No. 81-1543
      - Crisafi v. Keenan, No. 81-1558
      - Allard v. Gray, No. 81-1569
      - American Fed. of Gov't Employees, Local 1923 v. Federal Labor Relations Auth., No. 81-1583
      - Page v. Harris-Teeter Supermarkets, No. 81-1588 (Box 86)
      - Jonak v. Central Intelligence Agency, No. 81-1594
      - Chesapeake and Potomac Tel. Co. v. Landrieu, No. 81-1602
      - Solazzi v. Virginia Polytechnic Inst. and State Univ., No. 81-1617
      - Hopper v. Aetna Auto., Life and Casualty, No. 81-1642
      - Newport News Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Co. v. Green, No. 81-1668
      - Robertson v. Rogers, No. 81-1692
      - Harrison v. Ayers, No. 81-1707
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. G. F. Business Equip., No. 81-1726
      - Thomsson Steel Co. v. Crystal Gateway Corp., No. 81-1743
      - Strickland v. Baltimore City Law Dep't, No. 81-1744
      - United States v. A. & L. Mechanical Contractors, No. 81-1754
      - Burlington Indus. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 81-1758
      - Finlen v. Schweiker, No. 81-1767
      - Doe v. Wright, No. 81-1779
      - Omaha Indem. Co. v. United States, No. 81-1793
      - Burns v. Sharp, No. 81-1800
      - Rubel v. United States, No. 81-1803 (Box 87)
      - Harper v. Schweiker, No. 81-1854
      - Chertkof v. Maryland, No. 81-1862
      - McKinney v. Schweiker, No. 81-1903
      - Capers v. NCO Club, No. 81-1916
      - In re Allard, No. 81-1920
      - Hagedorn v. United Mine Workers Health and Retirement Fund, No. 81-1946
      - Spence v. Rodgers, No. 81-1956
      - Bordeaux v. Cumberland County Bd. of Educ., No. 81-1958
      - Frank's Hardware v. Frank's Nursery & Crafts, No. 81-1980
      - Glascow v. North Carolina Dep't of Transp., No. 81-1987
      - Harris v. West Virginia Secondary School, No. 81-1989
      - Van Gaalen v. Sparks, No. 81-2006
      - In re Paul, No. 81-2009
      - United States v. 290.47 acres, Prince George's County, Md., No. 81-2032
      - Brady v. Allstate Ins. Co., No. 81-2045
      - Rod Laver Tennis v. Bessemer Beach Properties, No. 81-2057
      - Andrews v. Commissioner, No. 81-2062
      - Union Oil Co. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 81-2094
      - Reese v. Briggs, No. 81-2110
      - Arrow Automotive Indus. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 81-2132
      - Farmer v. Roark, No. 81-2148
      - Tyler v. Schweiker, No. 81-2198
      - Keller v. Virginia Elec. & Power Co., No. 81-2199
      - Vander Zee v. Karabatsos, No. 81-2202 (Box 88)
      - Smith v. ACF Indus., No. 81-2204
      - Crawford v. Marshall, No. 81-2205
      - In re Grand jury proceedings, No. 81-2230
      - United States v. Mason, No. 81-5023
      - United States v. Lindsey, No. 81-5038
      - United States v. Stehl, No. 81-5066
      - United States v. King, No. 81-5111
      - United States v. Bennett, No. 81-5115
      - United States v. Howard-Arias, No. 81-5153
      - United States v. Odom, No. 81-5165
      - United States v. Manning, No. 81-5182
      - United States v. Keller, No. 81-5304
      - Ballard v. Thompson, No. 81-6002
      - Altizer v. Mitchell, No. 81-6031
      - Carroll v. Shaw, No. 81-6090
      - Bradwell v. Virginia, No. 81-6119
      - Anderson v. Morris, No. 81-6169
      - Braxton v. Dedmond, No. 81-6216
      - Gravely v. White, No. 81-6227
      - Mahler v. United States Bureau of Prisons, No. 81-6253
      - Pitts v. Hutto, No. 81-6258
      - United States v. Guillermo Calvillo-Flores, No. 81-6291
      - Holsey v. D'Alesandro, No. 81-6329
      - United States v. Gillis, No. 81-6340
      - Gaines v. Holt, No. 81-6354
      - Keil v. Mitchell, No. 81-6367
      - Davis v. Morris, No. 81-6406 (Box 89)
      - Evans v. North Carolina, No. 81-6411
      - Wortham v. Woodard, No. 81-6416
      - Grandison v. Maryland, No. 81-6439
      - United States v. Grandison, No. 81-6446
      - Anderson v. Moore, No. 81-6478
      - Wade v. Mitchell, No. 81-6501
      - Christian v. Johnson, No. 81-6545
      - Alston v. Murphy, No. 81-6555
      - Whitfield v. Brown, No. 81-6580
      - Creasy v. Bartram, No. 81-6592
      - Tyson v. Sutton, No. 81-6601
      - Bines v. Johnson, No. 81-6606
      - Williams v. Members of "Operation Ferret", No. 81-6618
      - Morgan v. Stoops, No. 81-6630
      - Chase v. Warden, Md. Penitentiary, No. 81-6635
      - Crowell v. Morris, No. 81-6651
      - Williams v. Guillen, No. 81-6656
      - United States v. Krohn, No. 81-6671
      - Boyd v. Bordenkircher, No. 81-6686
      - Pack v. Southampton Correctional Center, No. 81-6712
      - Page v. Mitchell, No. 81-6721
      - Thomas v. Warden, Md. State Penitentiary, No. 81-6753
      - Tweety v. Mitchell, No. 81-6771
      - Baines v. Mitchell, No. 81-6777
      - Rankins v. Hutto, No. 81-6797
      - Smith v. Morris, No. 81-6799
      - Eichman v. Dodson, No. 81-6804
      - Parker v. Morris, No. 81-6809
      - Herring v. Wallace, No. 81-6834
      - Muqsit v. Hutto, No. 81-6840
      - Hasen-Ahmad v. Hutto, No. 81-6873
      - Jones v. Mitchell, No. 81-6894
      - United States v. Hohman, No. 81-6900
      - Stokes v. Kegley, No. 81-6910
      - Medlock v. Gulmatico, No. 81-6915
      - Anger v. Garraghty, No. 81-6920
      - Bratten v. Smith, No. 81-6921
      - Smith v. General Assembly of Virginia, No. 81-6924
      - Graham v. Morris, No. 81-6934
      - Richardson v. Ray, No. 81-6940
      - Brown v. Hawkins, No. 81-6941
      - Smith v. Goodlander, No. 81-6955 (Box 90)
      - Bowman v. Winston, No. 81-6960
      - Rankins v. Hutto, No. 81-6970
      - United States v. Montgomery, No. 81-6974
      - Borders v. Reed, No. 81-6980
      - Vester v. Teague, No. 81-6989
      - United States v. Young, No. 81-6997
      - Lomax v. Swisher, No. 81-7005
      - Smith v. Monroe, No. 81-7007
      - Covington v. Garrison, No. 81-8046
      - Felder v. Parlett, No. 81-8130
      - Rallo v. Martin, No. 81-8135
      - Young v. Sams, No. 81-8138
      - Harrison v. Styles, No. 81-8191
      - Houston v. Bordenkircher, No. 81-8201
      - Moore v. Garrison, No. 81-8210
      - Thompson v. Wyant, No. 81-8226
      - Williams v. Hutto, No. 81-8232
      - Adams v. Bordenkircher, No. 81-8244
      - Norwood v. Woodard, No. 81-8278
      - Easterling v. Garrison, No. 81-8290
      - Carter v. Garrison, No. 81-8294
      - Jones v. Blankenship, No. 81-8305
      - Deckerhoff v. Hutto, No. 81-8310
      - Barbour v. Ross, No. 81-8325
      - Basden v. Attorney Gen., N.C., No. 81-8328
      - Fleming v. Johnson, No. 81-8334
      - Audia v. Bordenkircher, No. 81-8348
      - Carroll v. Allsbrook, No. 81-8361
      - Bratcher v. Evans, No. 82-1011
      - Hettleman v. Block, No. 82-1072
      - Warth v. West Virginia State Radiologic Technology Bd. of Examiners, No. 82-1077
      - Elmore v. Commissioner, No. 82-1140
      - Lay v. Bethlehem Steel, No. 82-1149
      - Price v. Block, No. 82-1315
      - Richmond Hilton Assocs. v. City of Richmond, No. 82-1364
      - United States v. Branscome, No. 82-5006
      - Henry v. Miller, No. 82-6010
      - O'Haire v. Peed, No. 82-6020
      - United States v. Kirk, No. 82-6039
      - Moore v. Medical, No. 82-6042
      - Cromartie v. Mack, No. 82-6051 (Box 91)
      - Johnson v. Hutto, No. 82-6062
      - Blanchard v. Horan, No. 82-6063
      - Dodson v. Morris, No. 82-6067
      - Pearson v. Hutto, No. 82-6068
      - Davis v. Watson, No. 82-6069
      - Robinson v. City of Greensboro, No. 82-6071
      - Pardue v. Williams, No. 82-6078
      - Shah v. Hutto, No. 82-6085
      - Porter v. Caudill, No. 82-6092
      - White v. Virginia, No. 82-6198
      - Smith v. Hutto, No. 82-6207
      - Martin v. Warden, Md. Penitentiary, No. 82-6219
      - Turner v. Mitchell, No. 82-6222
      - Peters v. Kelly, No. 82-6261
      - Mitchell v. Morris, No. 82-6286
      - Smith v. Harris, No. 82-6325
      - Tinsley v. Tinney, No. 82-6340
      - United States v. Pettee, No. 82-6348
      - Pettee v. Kilpatrick, No. 82-6375
      - Williams v. Hutto, No. 82-6558
      - Slonaker v. Bordenkircher, No. 82-8006
      - Shefton v. Wayland, No. 82-8070
      - Dempsey v. Dale, No. 82-8115
      - Palmer v. Blankenship, No. 82-8129
    - 1982 October term
      - Flannery v. United States, No. 80-1563; (3 folders)
      - United States v. Dodson, No. 80-5140
      - Nichols Eng'g and Research Corp. v. Savoy Constr. Co., No. 81-1072
      - Adams v. Proctor & Gamble Mfg. Co., No. 81-1197; (3 folders) (Box 92)
      - American Original Corp. v. Jenkins Food Corp., No. 81-1561; (2 folders)
      - Allen v. Fidelity and Deposit Co., No. 81-1638
      - George v. Bolger, No. 81-1891
      - Farmer v. Deere & Co., No. 81-1930
      - Laboke v. Loudermilk, No. 81-1941
      - Durboraw v. Clem Lamaster, Inc., No. 81-1960
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. PPG Indus., No. 81-1992
      - Nasim v. DiPasquale, No. 81-2063
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Lodge No. 10, Int'l Ass'n of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, No. 81-2133
      - Rabon v. Cunningham, No. 81-2165
      - A. P. McAuley Co. v. Insurance Co. of N. Am., No. 81-2167
      - Shaklo v. S & S Mfg. Co., No. 81-2228
      - United States v. Jackson, No. 81-5096
      - United States v. Talbert, No. 81-5169 (Box 93)
      - United States v. Walker, No. 81-5201
      - United States v. Murphy, No. 81-5279
      - United States v. McCormick, No. 81-5286
      - United States v. Cifaldi, No. 81-5295
      - United States v. Mullins, No. 81-5305
      - Williams v. Malicoat, No. 81-6414
      - Todd v. Baskerville, No. 81-6517
      - Turner v. Hutto, No. 81-6877
      - Paul v. Garrison, No. 81-6895
      - Isom v. Richtmyer, No. 81-6939
      - Keith v. Bordenkircher, No. 81-8371
      - Equal Employment Opportunity Comm'n v. Western Elec. Co., No. 82-1033
      - Watkins v. M. & M. Tank Lines, No. 82-1048
      - United States v. 37.05 acres of land, Wake County, N.C., No. 82-1082 (Box 94)
      - Afshar v. Commissioner, No. 82-1095
      - Iseley v. Leak Repairs, No. 82-1097
      - Fonda v. Commissioner, No. 82-1108
      - McCain Mfg. Corp. v. Rockwell Int'l Corp., No. 82-1111
      - Tenneco, Inc. v. First Virginia Bank, No. 82-1158; (2 folders)
      - Deal v. Newport Datsun Ltd., No. 82-1174
      - McNutt v. Duke Precision Dental and Orthodontic Laboratories, No. 82-1179
      - Sweeney v. Small World Creative Enters., No. 82-1241
      - Marshall v. Sisters of the Pallotine Missionary Soc'y, No. 82-1250
      - In re Braswell, No. 82-1270
      - 1616 Reminc Ltd. Partnership v. Atchison & Keller Co., No. 82-1284
      - Jones v. General Elec. Co., No. 82-1327
      - Foster v. Carolina Power and Light Co., No. 82-1345
      - Prudential Ins. Co. of Am. v. Tull, No. 82-1363
      - Moss v. Schweiker, No. 82-1386
      - Anderson v. Schweiker, No. 82-1387 (Box 95)
      - Clevepak Corp. v. United States Envtl. Protection Agency, No. 82-1390
      - Cooper v. United States, No. 82-1414
      - United States v. McCotter, No. 82-1438
      - Nanticoke Homes v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 82-1442
      - Lipkin v. Noonan, No. 82-1445
      - Parham v. Schweiker, No. 82-1466
      - Donovan v. Rockwell Tire & Fuel, No. 82-1484
      - Bostic v. United States, No. 82-1498
      - Central Transp. v. United States, No. 82-1504; (2 folders)
      - Barnhill v. School Bd., Tazewell County, No. 82-1537
      - Consolidation Coal Co. v. Local 1702, United Mine Workers, No. 82-1567
      - Hodson v. A. H. Robins Co., No. 82-1582; (2 folders)
      - Atherton v. Wachovia Servs., No. 82-1688
      - Sharma v. Atomic Prods. Corp., No. 82-1720
      - Taylor v. Nelson, No. 82-1737 (Box 96)
      - Warren v. Bakker, No. 82-1752
      - Hoechst Fibers Indus. v. Scott, No. 82-1789
      - Wells v. North Carolina Bd. of Alcoholic Control, No. 82-1796
      - Dallas v. Boyd, No. 82-1803
      - Gunter v. Nicholas County Community Action Ass'n, No. 82-1809
      - Allen M. Campbell Co. v. Virginia Metal Indus., No. 82-1845
      - Shehan v. Schweiker, No. 82-1919
      - Gilbert v. Bagley, No. 82-1941
      - Walton v. American Towing & Transp. Co., No. 82-1944
      - Gragg v. Colonial Mortgage Serv., No. 82-1974
      - Byers v. Schweiker, No. 82-1977
      - Medlin v. Schweiker, No. 82-1982
      - Elam v. Winston, No. 82-2016
      - Nickelson v. Schweiker, No. 82-2111
      - O'Malley v. Rapidan River Farm, No. 82-2121
      - United States v. Ruffin, No. 82-5036
      - United States v. Johnson, No. 82-5057
      - United States v. Smith, No. 82-5061
      - United States v. Tate, No. 82-5101
      - United States v. Mann, No. 82-5132
      - United States v. Hobby, No. 82-5143
      - United States v. Jones, No. 82-5209 (Box 97)